<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flexiride</string>

    <!--    sign up-->
    <string name="sign_up_text">Sign up</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="retype_new_password">Retype Password</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_terms_of_service_and_privacy_policy">I agree to Terms of Service and Privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_sign_in">Already have an account? Sign in</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="text_and_number">aAbBcCdDeEfFgGhHiIjJkKlLmMnNoOpPqQrRsStTuUvVwWxXyY zZ0123456789 æàáâäāåãçēêéèëìïíîīñõōòöóôßūüúûùÀÃÂĀÁÅĀÆÇĒÊÉÈËÌÏÍÎĪÑÕŌŒØÒÖÓÔẞŪÜÚÛÙ</string>
    <string name="only_text">aAbBcCdDeEfFgGhHiIjJkKlLmMnNoOpPqQrRsStTuUvVwWxXyY zZæàáâäāåãçēêéèëìïíîīñõōòöóôßūüúûùÀÃÂĀÁÅĀÆÇĒÊÉÈËÌÏÍÎĪÑÕŌŒØÒÖÓÔẞŪÜÚÛÙ</string>
    <string name="only_numbers"> 0123456789</string>
    <string name="enter_first_name">Please enter first name</string>
    <string name="enter_last_name">Please enter last name</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="password_8_20">Enter atleast 8-20 characters, 1 Uppercase, 1 lowercase and 1 Number</string>
    <string name="enter_retype_pass">Please retype password</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_email_add">Please enter valid email address</string>


    <!--    //home activity-->
    <string name="pick_up">Pick up</string>
    <string name="drop_off">Drop off</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="filter">FILTER</string>
    <string name="sort_by">Sort By</string>
    <string name="tuvs_available_yet">You don\'t have any cars available yet</string>
    <string name="rating_reviews">0 ratings and 0 reviews</string>
    <string name="_0_0">0.0</string>

    <!--    sign in -->
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account? Sign up</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome To Flexiride</string>
    <string name="i_m_an_owner">I\'m an Owner!</string>
    <string name="i_m_a_renter">I\'m a Renter!</string>

    <!--    //dashboard-->
    <string name="add_your_first_tuv">Add your first Car</string>
    <string name="view_details">View Details</string>
    <string name="accept">accept</string>
    <string name="reject">reject</string>

    <!--    basic details-->
    <string name="basic_info_title">Basic information about your car</string>
    <string name="tuv_brand">Car Brand</string>
    <string name="tuv_color">Car Color</string>
    <string name="tuv_model">Car Model</string>
    <string name="model_name">Enter model name</string>
    <string name="manufacturing_year">Manufacturing Year</string>
    <string name="license_plate_number">License plate number</string>
    <string name="licence_type">License Type</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="city">city</string>
    <string name="number_of_seats">number of seats</string>
    <string name="fuel_type">Fuel Type</string>
    <string name="gear_box">Gear Box</string>
    <string name="engine">Engine</string>
    <string name="tell_more">Tell us more about your car</string>
    <string name="text_continue">Continue</string>

    <string name="model_name_error">Please enter model name</string>
    <string name="manu_year_error">Please select manufactured year</string>
    <string name="license_plate_error">Please enter license plate number</string>
    <string name="brand_name_error">Please select brand</string>
    <string name="color_name_error">Please select color</string>
    <string name="tuv_type_error">Please select type</string>
    <string name="engine_cc_error">Please enter engine data</string>
    <string name="county_error">Please enter County</string>
    <string name="city_error">Please enter City</string>
    <string name="seat_error">Please enter number of seats</string>
    <string name="fuel_error">Please enter Fuel type</string>
    <string name="gear_error">Please enter Gear type</string>

    <!--    category select default-->
    <string-array name="array_name">
        <item>Select category</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select city-->
    <string-array name="array_city">
        <item>Select City</item>
        <item>Birmingham</item>
        <item>Bradford</item>
        <item>Bristol</item>
        <item>Cambridge</item>
        <item>Chester</item>
        <item>Coventry</item>
        <item>Leeds</item>
        <item>Leicester</item>
        <item>Liverpool</item>
        <item>London</item>
        <item>Manchester</item>
        <item>Norwich</item>
        <item>Nottingham</item>
        <item>Oxford</item>
        <item>Plymouth</item>
        <item>Portsmouth</item>
        <item>Sheffield</item>
        <item>Southampton</item>
        <item>St Albans</item>
        <item>Westminster</item>
        <item>York</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select gear-->
    <string-array name="array_gear">
        <item>Select Gear</item>
        <item>Automatic</item>
        <item>Manual</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select default-->
    <string-array name="array_fuel">
        <item>Select Fuel</item>
        <item>Petrol</item>
        <item>Diesel</item>
        <item>Electric</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select seats-->
    <string-array name="array_seats">
        <item>Select Seats</item>
        <item>02</item>
        <item>04</item>
        <item>06</item>
        <item>07</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select color-->
    <string-array name="array_color">
        <item>Select Color</item>
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Black</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Silver</item>
        <item>Gray</item>
        <item>Brown</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Beige</item>
        <item>Purple</item>
        <item>Gold</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    category select brand-->
    <string-array name="brand_name">
        <item>Select Brand</item>
        <item>Alfa Romeo</item>
        <item>Alpine</item>
        <item>Aston Martin</item>
        <item>Audi</item>
        <item>Bentley</item>
        <item>BMW</item>
        <item>Bugatti</item>
        <item>Cadillac</item>
        <item>Chevrolet</item>
        <item>Datsun</item>
        <item>Ferrari</item>
        <item>Fiat</item>
        <item>Ford</item>
        <item>Honda</item>
        <item>Hyundai</item>
        <item>Jaguar</item>
        <item>Jeep</item>
        <item>Kia</item>
        <item>Lamborghini</item>
        <item>Land rover</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--    add package-->
    <string name="fare_amount">Fare amount Per hour</string>
    <string name="numbers_decimal"> 0123456789.</string>
    <string name="for_duration">For duration</string>
    <string name="start_date">Start Date</string>
    <string name="end_date">End Date</string>
    <string name="search_location">Search Location</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>

    <string name="fare_amt_error">Please enter Fare amount</string>
    <string name="duration_error">Please enter duration </string>

    <!--    add photos-->
    <string name="add_tuv_photos">Photos of your Car</string>
    <string name="add_photos_title">Make sure you take nice pictures of your car so that customer can see car before selecting.</string>
    <string name="add_upto">You can add up to 4 photos of Car</string>
    <string name="you_have_no_photos_yet_click_on_add_photos_of_tuv">You have no photos yet. Click on add photos of car</string>
    <string name="added_tuv_photos">Added Car Photos</string>
    <string name="car_model">Car model</string>

    <!--   car details Key feature item-->
    <string name="_5_seats"> 5 Seats</string>
    <string name="seats">Seats</string>
    <string name="Key_Specifications"> Key Specifications</string>
    <string name="packages">Package</string>
    <string name="booking_amount">Payment Details</string>
    <string name="fare_amount_for_1_day">Fare amount for 1 day</string>
    <string name="total_fare_amount">Total fare amount</string>
    <string name="view_bookings">View Bookings</string>
    <string name="verify_your_data_to_get_started">Verify Your Data to get started</string>
    <string name="from_date">From Date</string>
    <string name="to_date">To Date</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select Date</string>


    <!-- booking confirmed-->
    <string name="booking_confirmed">Booking Confirmed</string>
    <string name="your_booking_id_is">Your booking ID is</string>
    <string name="have_a_wonderful_ride">Have a wonderful ride.</string>
    <string name="Note_your_booking">Note your booking ID for future reference</string>

    <string name="disclaimer">Insurance Verification Disclaimer

The Flexiride App ("the App") provides a platform for vehicle owners to list their cars for rental and for renters to find and book vehicles. While we strive to ensure a safe and reliable experience, we want to make it clear that the App does not verify or validate insurance details provided by users.

User Responsibility:

Verification: All users are responsible for independently verifying the insurance coverage of any vehicle they intend to rent or list on the App. This includes ensuring that the insurance policy covers the intended use, drivers, and circumstances.

Liability: Flexiride does not assume any responsibility for insurance-related matters between users. Any insurance claims, disputes, or issues that may arise are solely the responsibility of the parties involved.

Compliance: Users must comply with all local, state, and national laws and regulations related to insurance requirements for vehicle rentals.

Seek Professional Advice:

If you have any questions or concerns about insurance coverage or requirements, we strongly recommend seeking advice from a qualified insurance professional. Flexiride does not provide insurance advice or services.

By using the App, you acknowledge and agree to the terms of this insurance verification disclaimer. It is your responsibility to exercise due diligence and ensure that you are adequately covered by insurance when using the App for vehicle rentals or listings.</string>

    <string name="privacy">
Privacy Policy for Flexiride App

This Privacy Policy outlines how your personal information is collected, used, and protected when you use the Flexiride mobile application ("the App"). Flexiride is committed to ensuring the privacy and security of your personal data. By using the App, you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

1. Information We Collect

User Registration: To use the App, you will need to create an account. We collect your name, email address, phone number, and password for account registration.

Vehicle Details: If you are an owner listing a vehicle, we will collect information about your vehicle, including make, model, year, license plate number, images, and availability.

Location Information: We may collect your location information to provide rental options in your vicinity. You can enable or disable location services through your device settings.

Transaction Data: For rental bookings and payments, we collect transaction details, including payment method, billing information, and rental history.

2. How We Use Your Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

User Authentication: To create and manage your account and verify your identity when you log in.

Providing Services: To facilitate car rentals, bookings, and payments between users and owners.

Communication: To send important updates, notifications, and customer support responses.

Improving Services: To enhance and personalize your experience, we use your data to analyze usage patterns and make improvements to the App.

3. Data Protection and Security

We prioritize the security of your data and employ industry-standard security measures to safeguard your information. We encrypt sensitive data and regularly update our security protocols.

4. Data Retention

We retain your data for as long as it is necessary to provide our services, fulfill legal obligations, or resolve disputes. When you delete your account, we securely delete your data from our systems.

5. Sharing of Information

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may share data with service providers, partners, or law enforcement agencies when required by law.

6. Your Choices

You can access, correct, or delete your personal information at any time through your account settings. You can also choose to receive or opt out of promotional emails from us.

7. Changes to Privacy Policy

Flexiride may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices or for legal compliance. We will notify users of any significant changes.

8. Contact Us

For questions, concerns, or requests related to your privacy or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at developer@email.com.

By using the Flexiride App, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to its terms and conditions.</string>


    <string name="terms"><b>Flexiride App - Terms and Conditions</b>

These Terms and Conditions ("Terms") govern your use of the Flexiride mobile application ("the App"). By using the App, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree with any part of these Terms, please do not use the App.

1. User Registration

1.1. To use the App, you must create an account. You agree to provide accurate and complete information during the registration process.

1.2. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials, including your password. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your account.

1.3. You must notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security.

2. Use of the App

2.1. The App is intended for personal, non-commercial use only. You agree not to use the App for any illegal or unauthorized purpose.

2.2. You may not modify, adapt, or hack the App or any associated servers.

2.3. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Apps user accounts, systems, or networks.

2.4. You may not harass, abuse, or harm other users of the App.

3. Vehicle Listings and Rentals

3.1. Vehicle Owners: If you list a vehicle on the App, you agree to provide accurate and up-to-date information about your vehicle, including make, model, year, license plate number, and images.

3.2. Renters: If you rent a vehicle through the App, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions set by the vehicle owner, including rental duration, pricing, and return conditions.

4. Payment and Fees

4.1. Payments made through the App are processed by third-party payment providers. You agree to their terms and conditions when making payments.

4.2. Flexiride may charge service fees, which will be clearly communicated to you before completing a transaction.

5. Cancellations and Refunds

5.1. Cancellation policies are set by vehicle owners. Flexiride is not responsible for refunds or disputes related to cancellations.

6. User Conduct

6.1. You agree not to use the App to transmit any content that is unlawful, offensive, or harmful.

6.2. You may not engage in any activity that disrupts or impairs the Apps functionality or security.

7. Termination

7.1. Flexiride reserves the right to terminate or suspend your account and access to the App at any time, with or without cause.

8. Privacy

8.1. By using the App, you agree to the collection and use of your information as outlined in our Privacy Policy.

9. Changes to Terms

9.1. Flexiride may update these Terms at any time. You will be notified of significant changes. Continued use of the App after changes are made constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms.

10. Contact Us

10.1. For questions, concerns, or inquiries about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at developer@email.com.

By using the Flexiride App, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to these Terms and Conditions and that you will comply with all applicable laws and regulations.</string>

</resources>